几周之前 一个隐形的穹顶从天而降
A few weeks ago an invisible crashed dome crashed down
罩住了彻斯特磨坊镇 把我们和外部世界隔绝开来
on Chester's Mill, cutting us off from the rest of the world.
穹顶是怎么来的 其中蕴含着什么奥秘
Why the dome is here, what mysteries lie ahead,
我们还不知道
we still don't know.
每一天都试探着我们的底线
Every day it tests our limits,
我们内心深处的善与恶 一览无余
bringing out the best and the worst in us.
有人说我们会永远被困在这里面
Some say we'll be stuck here forever,
但是 我们决不放弃 坚持寻找逃出穹顶之法
but we will never stop fighting to find a way out.
哦 汉特 梅 这是我儿子戴尔
Oh, Hunter May, meet my son Dale.
我们需要你施展魔力
We need you to work your magic.
再发一条信息
to send one more message
到穹顶里面
into the dome
-芭比 -别跳
- Barbie! - Don't jump!
芭比
Barbie!
也许抓走芭比的
Maybe the guys who took Barbie
就是那些觊觎蛋的人
are the same ones who want the egg.
他们是怎么知道的
How would they even know about it?
我们要保护好它
We'll protect it.
最安全的地方
No better place to hide
就是躲到我爸的眼皮底下
than right under my dad's nose.
你们都认为是它驱动着穹顶
And you all think it powers the dome?
这就是它运行的机理 是吗
That's the-the working theory, right?
是的
Yeah.
我的职责就是带领镇上的人们
It's my job to lead the people
重获自由
of this town to freedom.
你是谁
Who are you?
她是我的一个朋友 波林 佛多
She's a friend of mine... Pauline Verdreaux.
-波林 雷尼 -吉姆的母亲
- Pauline Rennie? - James' mother.
我觉得那扇门是通往穹顶的
I think that door's the way back into the dome.
我知道它在哪儿 就出现在那里
I know where this is. Grew up there.
好的 我们走 走
All right. Let's go, let's go.
神马情况
What the hell?
不知怎的我们回来了
We're back somehow.
波林
Pauline?
是我
It's me.
这不可能 你
That's impossible. You...
你在这儿干什么
What are you doing here?
是穹顶把你传过来的吗
Did the dome send you?
像琳达和杜迪那样过来折磨我
Like Linda and Dodee to torment me?
什么
What?
不是的 吉姆
No, Jim.
是真正的我
It's really me.
不 不
No, no.
不 你已经死了
No. You died.
你九年前就已经死了
You died nine years ago.
我一直没有死
I was never dead.
你的车撞到了树上
You drove your car into a tree.
残骸我都看到了
I... I saw the wreck.
我还看到了新闻报导
I read the report.
还是我取出了你的骨灰
I picked out your casket.
我并不在那辆车里面
I was never inside the car.
车里面坐的是一具死尸
It was a cadaver.
莱斯特 科金斯 帮我伪造的 莱尔也帮了我
Lester Coggins helped me. And Lyle, too.
他知道用什么方法可以让整辆车烧起来
He knew what to use to make the car burn
烧得一无所剩
so that there would be nothing left.
-这是唯一的办法了 -什么唯一的办法
-It was the only way! -The only way for what?
这是逃离彻斯特磨坊镇的唯一办法
It was the only way to get out of Chester's Mill!
我跟你说过我的预感
I told you about my visions.
你也看过我画的画
You saw my paintings.
我知道肯定会发生可怕的事情
I knew something terrible was coming.
然后你就自己逃走了 抛弃了我和朱尼尔
So you ran away and left me and Junior?
我这么做是为了保护我的家人
To protect my family.
我以为穹顶是跟着我走的
I thought the dome would follow me.
而且你绝对不会允许我离开
And you would never let me go!
你竟然还有脸站在这儿
You're gonna stand here
站在你儿子的房间 在我面前找借口
in your son's room and make excuses to me?
别说了
Stop it.
是你毁了他 波林
You destroyed him, Pauline.
-你毁了你自己的儿子 -别再说了
- You destroyed your own son. - Stop.
这么多年了
For all these years,
我还以为是我的错
I thought it was my fault.
吉姆
Jim...
Jim?
可是我又回来了
I came back.
吉姆 我回来呀
Jim, I came back!
嗨
Hey.
看看这个
Look at this.
看到奇怪的东西了吗
See anything strange?
叶子枯萎了
Its leaves have turned.
就好像秋天一样
Like it's fall.
可是现在是夏天
Except it's summer.
过去两天气温骤降
The temperature's dropped in the last two days.
这是棵橡树
This is an oak.
是最先发生变化的树
One of the first to change.
你觉得是什么情况
Any idea why this is happening?
不知为何 穹顶加速了季节变迁
Somehow the dome is accelerating the seasons.
往常 秋天是我的最爱
Normally, fall's my favorite.
在火炉边上看书 再来杯加州葡萄酒 但是
Book by the fire, nice glass of pinot, but...
这太奇怪了
this is just odd.
噢我的天
Oh, my God!
茱莉亚
Julia?
-你回来了 -是的
- You came back. - I did.
我要带所有人出去
I'm gonna get everybody out.
怎么回事
What happened?
你怎么会在这儿
How are you here?
芭比 你特么怎么回来的
Barbie, how the hell did you get back?
我们到屋里说吧
Let's talk inside.
外面冻死人了
It's freezing.
这儿是什么时候变成阿拉斯加的
Since when did it become Alaska in here?
这还真不是个玩笑
No kidding.
而且 嗯
And, uh...
梅勒妮不在
Melanie's not here.
朱尼尔也不在
Junior either.
这个地方完全属于咱俩
We have the whole place to ourselves.
我们最好互相取个暖
Better keep each other warm.
等等 梅勒妮已经不在一天了
Wait. Melanie hasn't been here in, like, a day.
她可能在茱莉亚那儿
She's probably at Julia's.
或是在外面做简方达健身操
Or out doing Jane Fonda exercises,
或是80年代土老帽做的那些事
whatever people did in the '80s.
嗷 回来嘛
Oh, come back.
哦我的天 乔 蛋不见了
Oh, my God, Joe. The egg is gone.
啥
What?
你觉得是她拿的吗
You think she took it?
从她这么尽力保护这个蛋来看 我打赌是她拿的
The way she protects that thing, I bet she did.
走 我们去找她
Come on, let's go find her.
朱尼尔
Junior?
噢 对不起
Oh. Sorry.
我不是有意吓你的
I didn't mean to scare you.
没事儿
It's okay.
我该走了
I should go.
茱莉亚一定在担心了
Julia might be worried.
我不该让我们俩都睡着的
I shouldn't have let us fall asleep.
如果她因为我没回家而发火的话 我就把责任推到你身上
If she's mad I didn't come home, I'll just blame it on you.
我就跟她说是你把我锁在这了
Tell her you locked me up down here.
什么
What?
我开玩笑的
I-I was just kidding.
嗯
Um...
你确定蛋在这下面会安全吗
you're sure the egg's safe down here?
这个地方是为抵挡原子弹而建的
Uh, this place is built to withstand nuclear bombs.
是镇上最安全的地方了
It's the safest place in town.
好吧
Well...
那我们一会儿见
I guess I'll see you later.
好的 一会儿见
Uh, yes. See you later.
朱尼尔
Junior!
安琪
Angie?
你想想你到底在做什么
Think about what you're doing.
你是说和她在这下面
With her down here?
事情不是你想的那样
It-it's not what you think.
你是想跟着心走 还是免了
You're gonna want to follow your heart. Don't.
我不懂你在说什么
I-I don't know what you mean.
朱尼尔
Junior?
你刚说了啥
Did you say something?
没什么
No.
好的
Okay.
拜拜
Bye.
安琪
Angie?
穹顶之下
第二季  第十集
视频字幕由 SSK字幕组 制作发布
字幕只供学习 请勿做任何商业行为
敬请关注新浪微博@SSK字幕组
所以你跳下了一个地下的悬崖
So you jump off an underground cliff
翻译：小P 香蕉奶昔 Bunny  校对：小P Jophy
然后莫名其妙地到了顶点镇
and somehow land all the way in Zenith?
还在一个操场上醒来
Where you wake up on a playground.
我也觉得很惊讶
It surprised the hell out of me, too.
但同样的事也发生在山姆身上
But the same thing happened to Sam
还有莱尔
and Lyle.
时轴：络睿  压制：Beloved  总监：小P
那你还好吗 有没有身体上的受伤
And you feel okay? No physical injuries
或者什么心理障碍
or-or psychological disturbances?
到那的路很模糊 但
The way there was a blur, but...
但我醒过来了 我没事
but I woke up, I was fine.
回去的路
The way back...
我很久之前就有这个记忆
I had this memory from a long time ago.
什么
What?
只是一些
It was just something
我小时候的回忆
from when I was a kid.
其他人怎么样
How'd the others fare?
莱尔
Well, Lyle...
他没有和我们一起从水里出来
He didn't come up out of the water with the rest of us.
他死了吗
Is he dead?
我不知道
I don't know.
你知道的 也许他先上来了
You know, maybe he came up first.
也许他溺死了
He drowned.
又或者他陷在其中的某个地方
Or maybe he's trapped somewhere in between.
我不知道 最重要的是
I don't know. What matters is
我们能够利用那个悬崖
that we can use that cliff
把大家都带出去
to get everybody out of here.
但我们需要一个计划
But we need a plan.
我们最不想看到的就是混乱和惊逃
Last thing we want is a stampede.
我们先从我们信任的人开始
Let's start with the people we trust.
我会找汤姆和安德里亚
I will walkie Tom and Andrea.
让他们在一小时后在蔷薇酒吧见面
Have them meet us at the Sweetbriar in an hour.
好的
All right.
终于有可以出去的路了
There's finally a way out.
我不知道我们应不应该接受
And I don't know if we should take it.
梅勒妮
Melanie!
山姆
Sam?
你怎么还活着
How are you alive?
我在那次掉落中活了下来
I survived the fall.
听我说 我不是要回去伤害任何人
Listen, I'm not back to hurt anyone.
尤其是你
Especially you.
你杀了我
You killed me...
那天晚上不是我推你进那个坑里
I didn't push you into the crater that night.
所以那就是莱尔咯
So, it was Lyle?
是的
Yes.
我帮忙埋葬了你
I helped bury you.
我们都帮忙了 然后我们就跑走了
We all did. And then we ran.
从那天起我每天都在后悔
And I've regretted it every day since.
想象一下如果你相信我 保护好那个蛋
Imagine if you'd trusted me, and protected the egg.
也许这些事都不会发生
Maybe none of this would've happened.
也许穹顶也不会降下来
Maybe the dome wouldn't have come down.
也许也没有人会死
Maybe no one would've died.
梅勒妮
Melanie?
我真的很抱歉 梅勒妮
I am so sorry... Melanie.
为了所有的事
For everything..
我还有很多没完成的事
I have a lot of unfinished business.
我觉得这可能是我唯一的机会
And I figured this might be my only chance.
你永远不知道你还会有多少机会
You never know how many chances you're gonna get.
吉姆 你在做什么
Jim, what are you doing?
我只是在想
I was just thinking.
我们的事
About us.
我想也许我能把朱尼尔找出来
I thought maybe I'd find Junior out here.
这就像我离开的那一天
It's exactly as it was the day I left.
这是我让你活着的方式
It was my way of keeping you alive.
我常常来这里
I used to come out here and...
盯着这些 想要弄清楚
stare at these and try to figure out
是什么让你那么
what made you so...
疯狂
Crazy?
痛苦
Tormented.
你去了哪里 波林
Where were you, Pauline?
你怎么进到穹顶里的
How did you get inside the dome?
通过芭比家在顶点镇一座房子的地下室门
Through a cellar door on Barbie's family property in Zenith.
芭比吗 你在顶点镇看到戴尔和芭芭拉吗
Barbie? You saw Dale Barbara in Zenith?
我想这就是命运吧 他和我一起回来的
Fate, I guess. He came back with me.
还有山姆 我以前的一个学生
And Sam. And a former student of mine.
还有莱尔
And Lyle.
只是莱尔没有活下来
Except Lyle didn't make it.
听到这个消息我感到很难过
I'm sorry to hear that.
但为什么你会想要 来这里
But why would you want... to come here?
因为朱尼尔
For Junior.
还有你
And you.
我不应该就那样跑开
I shouldn't have run like that.
不管什么理由 我都做错了
Whatever my reasons, I was wrong.
不 你没错
No, you weren't.
你是对的
You were right.
关于粉色星星掉落 关于穹顶
About the pink stars falling, about the dome,
关于一切 所有的一切
about everything. All of it.
那时候的我不是个好男人 我知道
I wasn't a good man back then. I know that.
我没有听你说 我一直把你推开
I didn't listen, I kept pushing you away.
但穹顶告诉了我一些东西 一条新路成为一个好男人
But the dome has shown me things, a new way to be.
而现在它把你带回我身边
And now it's brought you back to me.
波林 我能 我能够证明给你看我变了
Pauline, I can... I can prove to you that I've changed.
吉姆 我不知道
Jim, I-I don't know.
你以前爱过我 不是吗
You loved me once before, didn't you?
是的 很爱很爱
Yes. Very much.
那么 我们能够重新组成家庭
Well, then we can be a family again.
我要带所有人离开这里
I'm gonna lead everyone out of here.
当一切都结束的时候 当你和我还有朱尼尔出来的时候
And when it's over, when you and me and Junior are out...
我们就能在一起了
we'll be together.
我一直相信这个穹顶是在保护我们
I have always believed that the dome is here to protect us.
如果现在它真的是呢
What if it still is?
可能它最初的意图真的是这样
Maybe it started out that way, okay?
但是现在我们几乎没有食物了
But there's barely any food left.
没有药物的供应
You got no medical supplies.
还有突然间 这里变得越来越冷
Now, all of a sudden, it's getting colder by the hour.
我知道
I realize that.
但莱尔不知道
But Lyle didn't make it.
我是说 如果一直有人试着出去然后死了的话 责任是在我们身上
I mean, if these people die getting out, that's on us.
我所能理解的是 我们呆在这就是死路一条
What I know is: we stay here, we die here.
顶点镇里在等着我们的是什么
And what's waiting in Zenith?
游乐场已经被监视了
The playground is under surveillance.
你被抓去严刑拷打
You were interrogated, beaten.
那是因为他们想要那个蛋
That's because they wanted the egg.
所以按我说 我们就把蛋给他们
So I say this: "Let's give it to 'em."
那个视频是我爸爸发的 是不是
My dad sent that video, right?
他在幕后操纵着这些事
He's behind this whole thing.
所以我想 我们给他所要的
So my thinking is, if we give him what he wants,
他们就不会再来烦我们
maybe they leave us alone.
所以我们要把蛋交出去吗
So... we leverage the egg.
我先去 跟他们说只要他们不来烦我们
I go first and I tell them that it's theirs,
蛋就是他们的了
so long as they let the whole town through.
然后你再带着蛋出现
You come last with the egg.
我要先去
I have to go first.
不 不 你不行
No. No, you're not, no.
我不会让你这么做的
There's no way I'm letting you do that...
如果你走不掉了怎么办
What would've happened if you hadn't escaped?
他们再抓到你结果会更糟糕
It'll be worse if they capture you again.
应该我先去
I should go.
茱莉亚 他们不会对你心慈手软的
Julia, they're not gonna go easy on you.
我应付得来
I can handle it.
如果你没收到我的短信说
And if you don't get a message
交易达成了 你就要呆在这里
agreeing to the deal, you'll be here.
-不 -这里的人需要你
- Mm-mm. - These people are gonna need you.
不 如果我没收到短信
No. If I don't get a message agreeing to the deal...
我就去找你
I come after you.
梅勒妮
Melanie.
你去了哪
Where were you?
我
I was...
你回来了
You're back!
嘿
Hey.
见到你真是太好了
It's good to see you.
梅
Mel.
蛋在哪
Where's the egg?
蛋
It's...
在安琪家不见了
gone from Angie's apartment.
但是 芭比已经回来了
But... but Barbie's here.
你还要蛋干嘛
Why do you want it?
它可以帮我们出去
Because it's our way out.
不
N-No.
很抱歉 茱莉亚 但是
I'm sorry, Julia, but...
我不能告诉你蛋在哪
I, I can't tell you where it is.
嘿
Hey.
我和你聊一聊好吗
Can I talk to you for a second?
我们四个人对蛋藏在哪里都有发言权
All four hands should have a say in where the egg is kept
梅勒妮也许现在就和蛋一起
and Melanie's probably
呆在她自己建的巢里面
sitting on it in a nest she built somewhere.
-所以我们得找到它然后抢回来 -怎么找
- So we'll find it and we'll take it back. - How?
茱莉亚和杜迪建造过一个类似瑜伽的工具
Well, Julia and Dodee built that yogi thing.
那一点用处都没有
It's a piece of crap.
是啊 所以我们要建个更好的
Yeah, so we'll build a better one.
你是谁
Who the hell are you?
你们好 我叫汉特
Hey. I'm Hunter.
你是乔麦克里斯特 视频博客的大师
And you're Joe McAlister, Vlog Master,
创建了耐得诺里网站 同时创造了
and @neithernorrie, slaying the world
一百四十个人物
a hundred and forty characters at a time.
好吧 你怎么知道我们是谁
Okay. How do you know who we are?
特别是 你 很显然
Especially since you've, apparently,
是凭空出现的
just popped up out of the ether.
你们在网上是名人
You guys are celebrities online.
我是和芭比一起从顶点镇来的
I just came from Zenith with Barbie.
芭比回来了
Barbie's back?
你们是特意回来的吗
You came here on purpose?
我没法拒绝近距离观察这个穹顶的诱惑
I wasn't about to turn down the chance to check out the dome.
我们是
It was a...
通过水路来的 我的手机竟然没事
watery arrival... but my phone survived...
但是这里没有信号
obviously there's no service,
但这是我网页的主页
but that is my site's homepage.
-戴安娜猎人 是你发邮件给我的 -是的
- Hounds of Diana. You e-mailed me. - Uh-huh.
你还在推特上给我发信息
And direct tweeted me.
是啊
Yeah.
汉特
Hunter.
你带着这堆东西在这在干嘛
What are you doing here with all of this stuff?
额 很明显我在试着和外界
Uh... desperately trying to, uh, establish contact
建立联系 但是 还没成功
with the outside world, but... no luck.
你们想要我帮忙追踪那个蛋在哪吗
Want help tracking down that egg?
你会读心术
Are you a mind reader?
我不会 你们在走廊上讲话很大声而已
No. You guys were loud coming down that hallway.
那个蛋的事你知道多少
What do you know about the egg?
我在阿克泰昂为芭比的爸爸工作
I... work for Barbie's dad at Aktaion.
那个蛋一直是很多会议的主题
That egg's been the subject of many of a meeting.
我说我们最好用一个声波测试仪
I'd say our best best's a sound wave detector.
所有的能源都有频率 即使我们听不到
All energy sources emit a frequency, even if we can't hear it.
应该可行
That could work.
你们认为我们可以找到一把雷达枪
Do you think we could get our hands on a radar gun?
警察局肯定有一把
Oh, the police station has to have one.
你们知道这里有什么可以吃的吗
Well, you guys know if there's anything to eat around there?
我只买到这个
Because all I brought was this?
给我 外面的食物
I call dibs. Food from the outside?
嘿
Hey.
用炸弹炸穹顶会怎么样
What did it feel like when the bomb hit this thing?
我会告诉你 不过你得先告诉我们你是怎么进来的
I'll tell you after you tell us how you got in here.
不 我不能告诉你蛋在哪
No. I can't tell you where the egg is.
就算
But ev-ev...
就算它是我们出去的唯一办法
even if it's our ticket out of here?
不行
No.
我之前看过这条项链
You know, I've seen that necklace before.
是啊 你是在他们埋了我的地方看见的
Yeah. You found it where they buried me.
我问你
Let me ask you...
你去过 额
Have you ever been to, uh...
顶点镇里的一个大的白色房子吗
a big white house in Zenith?
有一片大草地
There's a b-big lawn...
额
um...
泳池
pool...
还有地窖
there's a root cellar.
地窖门是红色的
With a red door.
红色的 是
With a red door, yeah.
我妈妈曾经带我去过那里
Yeah, and my mom brought me there once.
我整个下午都在和那个小男孩玩
I-I spent the afternoon playing with this little boy;
他真是可爱
he was so sweet.
我们把门油成红色的
We painted that door red
他把手印上去了
and he-he put his hand on it.
那就是我 梅勒妮
Yeah. That-that was me, Melanie.
那就是我 我就是那个小男孩
That was me... I was that boy.
但是 额 你怎么知道
Uh... but... uh... how do you know?!
我知道 因为我记得
I know, because I remember.
我就在那 我记得的
I, I was there, I remember.
我们在玩
We were, we were playing
然后你们有急事得走了
and then you-you had to leave in a hurry...
是啊 妈妈很不开心 她
Yeah. My mom was so upset, she...
那个 那个男孩的爸爸
That-that-that-that boy's dad...
额 你爸爸 他一直说
um... your... your dad, he kept saying,
劳拉 劳拉 我很抱歉
"Laura, Laura. I'm so sorry."
噢天哪
Oh, my God.
怎么了
What?
我的父母
My parents...
曾经为了一个叫做劳拉的女人吵架
used to fight about a woman named Laura,
因为我猜是我爸爸跟她
because I guess my dad was in-in-involved with her
在结婚前有一段往事
in a relationship before he married my mother.
你爸和我妈
Your dad and my mom?
是啊 他们
Yeah. They had...
他们有个女儿
they had a daughter together.
等等
Wait.
你是说
Are you saying that...?
我是说
I'm saying...
你是我的妹妹 梅勒妮
that you are my sister, Melanie.
原来这就是她带我来这里的原因
That's why she brought me there.
是为了在搬走前见你最后一面
To meet you before we moved.
她从来不告诉我爸爸是谁
She never would tell me who my father was.
这也是为什么你看起来很眼熟
It's why you looked so familiar.
是啊 这也是我在回来穹顶时
Yeah. And that's... that's why I had this memory
回忆起那些事的原因
on the way back into the dome.
这不是巧合 是有原因的
This wasn't a coincidence; there's a reason for this.
什么原因
What's the reason?
你和我注定要带着大家一起出去
You and I are supposed to lead people out of here,
去顶点镇 但我们需要那个蛋才能完成
into Zenith, but we need the egg to do that.
不 不
No. No.
不 我不能把它交出来
No, I-I can't give it up.
我 我知道如果我没有保护好它的话
I... I know something bad will happen
-会发生一些很糟的事 -梅勒妮
- if I don't protect it. - Melanie,
我不会让不好的事发生在你身上
I'm not gonna let anything bad happen to you.
跟我们一起去蔷薇酒吧好吗
Just come to Sweetbriar Rose with us, okay?
听我们解释
Hear us out.
好
Okay.
朱尼尔十八岁生日
Junior's 18th birthday.
我错过了太多我儿子的生活
I've missed so much of my son's life.
波林 你会参与到这个家庭不断成长
Pauline, you're gonna be... A part of everything
的每一件事中
that has to do with this family moving forward.
妈妈
Mom?
詹姆斯
Oh, James.
额
Uh...
詹姆斯
James...
噢
Oh...
你怎么现在在这
How... how are you here right now?
说来话长
It's a long story.
你
You can, um...
你可以在吃早餐的时候告诉他
you can tell him over breakfast, then.
你要去哪
Where are you going?
我是警长 我有责任维持这个小镇的安宁
I'm sheriff... I've got responsibilities to the town.
我要去 跟芭比讨论一下怎么出去
I got to... talk to Barbie about an exit strategy.
好好对待你妈 朱尼尔
Be good to your mom, Junior.
额 你要我煮点东西给你吃吗
Uh, d-do you want me to get you something to eat?
-不用了 我不饿 -我给你煮点东西吧
- No, no, I'm... I'm okay. - Come on, I'll make you something.
-你想吃什么 -不用了
- What do you like? - It's fine.
-妈 妈 停下来 -我可以做
- Mom, Mom, stop, stop. Stop. - Is there... You can have...
莱尔告诉我你为什么要走
Lyle told me why you left.
你看过那段视频但你没告诉吉姆
You saw the video and you didn't tell Jim?
不是 我不知道要怎么说
No. I didn't know how.
这是最好的办法
That's for the best.
你爸爸和我 我们不适合
Your father and I, we're not good for each other.
他认为我们又是一家人了
He thinks we're a family again.
如果这样能让我们出去的话 随他想吧
If that helps us get out, that's fine.
每个人都有回来的理由
Everybody had their reasons for coming back.
你是我的理由
You're mine.
芭比回来了 还有谁
Barbie's back. Who else?
山姆 你叔叔有太多要补偿的了
Sam. Your uncle has a lot to atone for.
他永远也弥补不了杀死安琪的罪恶
He can never do that for killing Angie.
他这么做是因为我在日记里写的东西
He only did it because of what I put in my journal.
你只是画了一幅画
You drew a picture!
他就跑去杀了个人
He murdered a girl.
你要去哪
Where are you going?
去警察局 我现在代替爸爸的职务
To the station... I'm Dad's deputy.
停下来
Make it stop!
Make it stop.
你想要每个人都跳崖吗
You want everyone to jump off a cliff?
做起来不想听起来那么疯狂
It's not as crazy as it sounds.
那个悬崖通往芭比去的地方 死亡
That cliff leads to the same place it did for Barbie: our deaths.
是通往顶点镇
It leads to Zenith.
我保证
I guarantee it.
噢 我不敢相信
Oh, I don't believe it.
听着 我们需要你和我们一起
Look, please, we need you guys on board
帮其他人逃出去
to help us get everyone out.
我们根据人口调查
We'll use the census.
把整个镇子分成几个小组 有各自的组长
We divide the town into groups, everyone gets a leader
还有有急救知识经验和混合不同年龄阶段的人
and someone with first aid experience and a mix of ages.
彻斯特磨坊镇是我们的家
Chester's Mill is our home.
我们不会强迫大家走
We're not forcing anyone to leave.
但是呆在这不是个好主意
But staying's a really bad idea.
你感觉到这有多冷了吗
You feel how cold it is?
这里的气候已经遭到破坏
Our microclimate's disrupted.
燃料在不断消耗 食物也不够了
With dwindling fuel and not enough food,
趁我们还有力气 我们得逃出去
we have to get out while we can.
在大吉姆同意这件事之前我不会做任何事
I'm not doing anything till I know where Big Jim stands on this.
你呢 汤姆
What about you, Tom?
我要做小组长
Sign me up as a leader.
这里的东西所剩无几了
There's nothing left for us here.
假设大家都相信我们
So, assuming people do take a leap of faith
跳下了悬崖 去了顶点镇之后我们要干嘛
and jump off the cliff, what happens when we get to Zenith?
计划是茱莉亚先走
Uh, the plan's for Julia to go first.
她先去和对方谈判
She's gonna lay out the terms.
谈判什么
Which are?
保证全部镇民的安全
Safe passage for the entire town.
一旦大家都走了 芭比
Once everyone else is out, Barbie
和梅勒妮就可以带走他们想要的东西
and Melanie will jump with what they want.
他们 说的是穿黑衣的士兵
"They" Being the soldiers in black.
他们要的东西
And what they want...
是那个蛋
is the egg.
我呢 在你的计划里面充当什么角色
And how do I fit into your little plan?
我也是镇民的一部分
'Cause I'm a part of it.
从现在开始算起
Starting now.
你就是在找这个吗
Is this what you're looking for?
就是它
That's it.
好了
Okay.
改变固件来对准中频输出
Changed the firmware to adjust the IF output.
好了 测试仪经过改良 音频范围扩大了
Yep. The wave guide's modified, enhancing the tonal range.
呃 翻译一下 好吗
Uh, translation from geek, please?
我们把它改造成探测高频率的测试仪了
We're making it pick up high-pitched frequencies
而不是探测移动
instead of movement.
噢 这个当然
Oh. Of course.
顺便说一下 我们出去之后 千万别跟我
By the way, once we get out? Don't mention any of this
的假释官说起这件事 她不会相信的
to my parole officer. She wouldn't approve.
等等 你的假释官
Wait. You have a parole officer?
攻击了世界五百强
Repercussion of exploiting the server vulnerabilities
的服务器漏洞
of Fortune 500 companies.
听起来好牛
Sounds awesome.
和进入穹顶比起来不算什么
Nothing compared to finding out what it's like under the dome.
真是好笑 我们都想知道
Ironic. All we want to know
穹顶外发生了什么
is what's happening outside of it.
好吧
Okay.
你看看
Well, you want to do the honors?
起作用了 蛋在西边这个方向
It works. The egg is somewhere to the west.
好的 那我们还在等什么呢
Okay, so, what are we waiting for?
赶紧去抢蛋啊
Let's go get that egg.
说真的 汉特 很感谢你帮我们改造这个东西
Actually, Hunter, thanks for helping us build this thing.
但 就到这里吧
But... that's as far as it goes.
是
Yeah.
不好意思
Unfortunately.
这是诺瑞和我该做的事
It's just something Norrie and I have to do alone.
哥们 不用担心
Dude, it's no worries. I...
其实我想去镇上逛一逛 照相
I actually want to go get some pictures around town
好放在我戴安娜猎人的网站上
for my Hounds of Diana Web site.
你不相信他
You don't trust him?
我只相信我们两个人
I-I-I trust us.
我们是四人中的两个
We're two of the four hands.
他不是
Not him.
你认为他会把蛋抢走
You really think he'd take the egg for himself?
他怎么知道学校里会有个柜子
And how would he know that there's a locker at the school
柜子里有悬崖可以让我们逃出彻斯特磨坊镇
that leads to a cliff that's the way out of Chester's Mill
我们跳下去就可以逃生
and we have to do is jump?
也许是芭比告诉他的
Maybe Barbie told him.
无论怎样 我们有信号
Anyway, we have a signal.
我们去找那个蛋吧
Let's find that egg.
所以 现在是怎样
So, what's the problem?
我们给他们蛋 就可以自由了
We give them the egg, we get our freedom.
我们得小心点 吉姆
We have to do this carefully, Jim.
外面的人总不能拘留两千个人吧
Whoever's out there's not gonna detain 2,000 people.
这是在美国
This is still America.
噢
- - Oh, oh.
你是在说想炸了这个穹顶的那群人吗
You mean the same people that bombed this place, right?
你都搞不清楚现在的状况
You-you don't even know what you're dealing with.
我知道什么对这个小镇来说是最好的
I know what's best for this town.
所以我要第一个走 去跟他们谈判
Which is why I'll be going first to negotiate.
你说什么
Excuse me?
我是警长
I'm the sheriff.
我是这里唯一称得上是官员的人
I'm the only elected official here.
你还是个汽车销售员
You're also a lifelong used car salesman.
没错
That's right.
所以我知道怎么讨价还价
Which means I know how to cut a deal.
无论你们是喜欢我还是讨厌我 都由我来做这件事
Love me or hate me, I get things done.
你一家人都在这里 不是吗
Your whole family's here now, right?
让他先上
He goes first.
让他先上 让他们留下来
He goes first, they stay behind.
这样的话 无论如何他都必须
That way he's got every reason
保证我们所有人都安全出去
to make sure that we all get through safely.
好吧
Fine.
好吧 你先上
Fine. Go first.
但必须等到整个镇上的人都得到通知
But not until the entire town has been informed
同时逃生小组也都各就各位
and the exit teams are in place.
这些都由你们来决定吧
I'll leave that in your hands.
你们尽快把话传出去
Spread the word as fast as you can.
你都听到了吧
You heard it.
全盘计划都赖于我们带上蛋
The whole plan depends on taking the egg with us.
你说呢 梅勒妮
What do you say, Melanie?
波林 我们该走了 我搞定了
Pauline, we're leaving! I worked it out.
你 我 朱尼尔 我们可以从这逃出去了
You, me and Junior, we're getting out of here.
我们要自由了
We're gonna be free.
马上就出来了 马上 就快出来了
It's coming soon, soon. It's coming.
你在
What are you...?
哦我的天啊
Oh, my God.
这是一切一切的结局 吉姆
It's the end of everything, Jim.
我脑中已经预见了
I see it in my head.
那是你 我 和朱尼尔
That's you, me and Junior.
我的头 快让它停下
My head... make it stop!
这是下一步会发生的事情吗
Is this what's gonna happen next? （去掉了-号）
我们一家人会有危险
Is our family in danger?
嗷 好疼啊 快让它停下
Oh, it hurts. Make it stop.
-让什么停下 -我的头
-Make what stop? - My head.
-头的哪里疼 让什么停下 -快让它停下
- What's hurts? Make what stop? - Make it stop.
-你在说什么 -那个蛋 蛋在尖叫
- What are you talking about? - The egg. It's screaming.
那个蛋 那 它放在哪里 什么
The egg? Well, where is it? What...?
真的假的 你听不到吗难道
Really? You can't hear that?
-我在听 我在听 可我确实听不到 -噢神啊
- I'm trying! I'm trying! I can't hear it... - Oh, God!
你还是老样子 总是不相信我
You haven't changed. You don't believe me.
和过去一模一样
Just like always.
我和过去不一样了 我真的相信你
I have changed. I do believe you.
你画的每件事都成真了
Everything you painted has came true.
我相信你啊 我只是 我
I believe you, I just... I can't...
-快停下 快停啊 -宝贝儿宝贝儿宝贝儿 冷静一点
- Stop. Stop it. - Babe, babe, babe, calm down.
-快让它停下 快停下 -静一静 镇定 镇定点
- Stop it! Stop it! - Calm down! Calm down! Calm down!
-冷静一点 -你走开啊
- Calm down! - Get out of here!
走开
Get out!
-镇定 -走开
- Calm down... - Get out!
我在帮你啊
I'm trying to help.
滚啊 啊啊啊
Get out! Aah!
静一静 我 我来帮你
Just calm down! I'll-I'll help you!
我 我去找人帮忙 我保证
I'll-I'll get help, I promise.
别 别 别 别 别
No, no, no, no, no!（去掉了calm down）
别啊 别把我锁在这儿 求你了
No! Don't lock me in here, please!
别把我锁在这儿
Don't lock me in here!
我要保证你的安全
I'm trying to keep you safe.
别啊 别把我锁在这儿
No! Don't lock me in here!
听着 我会把我们俩都弄出去的 我保证
Listen, I'll get us out of here, I promise!
-我和一个人谈好了 好吗 -吉姆 求你了
- I made a deal with a guy, okay? - Jim, please!
-求求你 -他会照顾好我们的家人的
- Please! - He's gonna take care of our family.
-我保证他会带我们逃出去 -不 不
- I promise he'll get us out of here! - No, no!
相信我
Trust me!
现在要去找到那该死的蛋
Just got to find that damn egg.
这事儿她也说对了
She was right about this, too.
你让我拿着蛋过去
You'll let me carry the egg over?
对的 我会全程陪同
Yeah, I-I will be beside you the entire time.
我们真的要把蛋给那些外面的人吗
Do we really have to give it to those people out there?
只要咱爸看到你还活着
Once our dad sees you alive again,
他唯一关心的就是这个
that is all he's gonna care about.
而不是什么蛋
Not some egg.
让我考虑一下
I need a minute.
你刚才是不是做了无法兑现的承诺
Did you just make a promise you can't keep?
刚才那种情况 什么事都由她说了算
Right now, this is all riding on her
还有大吉姆 掌控谈话权
and Big Jim talking the talk.
-好吧 效果还不错 -我晓得
- Oh, that actually worked out well. - I know.
他对你爸来说什么都不算
He doesn't mean anything to your dad.
我们都不值得去冒这个险
And now neither one of us has to risk being nabbed.
嗨
Hey.
你动摇了吗
Are you having second thoughts?
不 还是想逃出去
Not about leaving.
不
No.
那你犹豫什么
About what?
我们是因为穹顶才认识的
We met because of the dome.
而且我们从来没有对彼此谈过
And we never really talked about you and me
逃到外面的世界之后作何打算
out in the world.
哦哦
Oh.
茱莉亚
Julia.
喂
Hey.
我希望你能一直陪在我左右
I want you in my life
无论我们能否逃到顶点镇
whether we end up in Zenith
或是在其它任何地方
or wherever.
这个承诺我一定兑现
That's a promise that I can keep.
-好 -伙计们
- Good. - MELANIE: Guys.
你们到底要不要这个蛋
You want the egg or not?
-就是这儿 -我们拿着它 离开这个该死的地方
- That's it. - Let's get it and get the hell out.
为什么蛋在尖叫
Why is it screaming?
有东西吓到它了
Something's scaring it.
看来不是我们吓着它了 你把它安抚下来了
It's not us. You calmed it down.
现在我们该走了
Now it's time to go.
去哪儿
Where?
到学校下面的悬崖去
The cliff under the school.
要把这玩意儿带去顶点镇
That thing's going to Zenith.
芭比回来了 我们没必要那么做了
Barbie's back. There's no reason.
没得商量
It's not a debate.
我没必要听你的
I don't have to do anything you say.
你说的是
You're right.
不过如果你不听 我就朝他开枪
You don't, I'm gonna shoot him.
你别管我 诺瑞
Don't worry about me, Norrie.
最重要的是保护好蛋
All that matters is protecting the egg.
你不会朝乔开枪的
You wouldn't shoot Joe.
和我对着干的人有一大串
There's a long list of people who've gone against me.
我不介意加乔麦克里斯特一个
I got no problem adding Joe McAlister to it.
我们走
Let's go.
马上归西了你倒还算冷静
Pretty calm for a dead man.
我知道你会过来
I figured you'd stop by.
我不希望我会是这种结局
I hope it doesn't have to end this way.
安琪倒是希望她的结局不是你
Angie hoped it wouldn't end with you
在她头上砍了一斧子
swinging an axe down on her head.
我以为那样会瓦解穹顶
I thought it would bring the dome down.
如果能让时光倒流 我愿意付出一切
I would do anything to take it back.
你把她的手镯放到我的枕头下面 诱使我以为
You put her bracelet under my bed so I'd think
我失去理智把她杀了
I blacked out and killed her.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我当时不知所措了
I didn't know what else to do.
不用担心了
Don't worry.
很快就了结了
It'll be over soon.
朱尼尔 我无法让时光倒流
Junior, I can't take back what I've done.
但你还是可以做做好事的
You still have a choice.
你说的是
You're right.
用子弹杀你 太便宜你了
Bullet's too quick.
我要让你生不如死
- You still have to suffer. -
站起来
Get up.
Get up!
打我啊 快反击啊
Hit me. Fight back.
反击啊
Fight back.
快反击
Fight back!
反击啊
- Fight back! -
你对安琪所做的
I'm gonna do to you...
我也要让你尝尝滋味
what you did to Angie.
朱尼尔 快停手
Junior, stop!
信号呢
Where is the signal?
闭嘴
Shut up.
走着
Keep going.
好的 我们走
All right, let's go.
穿过橱柜 去悬崖那儿 快
Through the locker and to the cliffs. Come on.
你不能杀他
You can't kill him.
你凭什么回来 还来维护他
How can you come back and protect him?
留着山姆还有用
Sam still has a part to play.
还有我们的双手
So does each of the hands.
如果他死了 穹顶里的每个人都会受连累
If he dies, everyone under the dome will suffer.
我爱你 他却把你从我这儿夺走了
I loved you, and he took you away from me.
你从来没爱过我
You never loved me.
你把我锁起来 想要囚禁我
You locked me up, wanting to keep me.
那不是爱
That's not love.
那只是占有欲
That is possession.
你何苦要做这些傻事
Why do something that can't be undone
去报复一个甚至都不是真实存在的爱人
to avenge a love that wasn't even real?
你不是真的
You're not real.
你只是穹顶和我玩的把戏
You're just the dome playing tricks on me.
朱尼尔 我在告诉你不要去做
Junior, I'm telling you not to do this.
看着我
Look at me.
不要这么做
Don't do it.
就当为了我
For me.
看着我
Look at me.
Look at me!
不
No!
看到了吗 安琪
See, Angie?
我是真的爱你
I really did love you.
这太可怕了 我们应该怎么做
It's freaking out. What are we supposed to do?
不要扔掉蛋
Do not throw the egg.
如果那是穹顶的能量源
If that's the power source to the dome,
我们都会死
we could all die.
如果我不扔的话 他会杀了你
If I don't, he'll kill you.
谈话就此结束
That's enough talking.
那东西必须得丢弃 就现在
That thing needs to go, now.
看它
Look at it.
它不想我扔掉
It doesn't want me to.
也许它是不想呆在这里呢
Well, maybe it doesn't want to be here.
这关乎我的家庭
This is about my family.
现在你得扔了它
Now, you throw it over now.
那剩下的我们呢
What about the rest of us?
你总是说你爱切斯特磨坊镇的每一个人
You've always said you love everybody in Chester's Mill.
我是
I do.
那就不要逼我们这么做
Then don't make us do this.
我的妻子很痛苦
My wife is suffering.
每个人也都会出去的 好吗
And everybody's gonna get out, too, okay?
但那个蛋现在就得丢弃
But that egg needs to go now.
看到了吗
See?
没有人死
Okay, no one's dying.
什么事都没有
Everything's okay.
-乔
- Joe! -
跑 快跑
Run. Run!
它原本就在这里 就在这里
It was right here, it was right here!
好了 我们得走了
Okay, we gotta go!
-朱尼尔拿了吗 -我不知道
- Junior took it? - I don't know!
我们走吧 好了 快点
Let's go! Okay, come on!
不
No!
梅勒妮
Melanie!
她怎么了
What's wrong with her?
我不知道 她几乎都没有呼吸了
I don't know. She's barely breathing.
帮我抬她起来
Help me get her up.
快来人 救我
Come on, help me!
嘿 我还在这下面
Hey, I'm down here!
快来啊
Come on!
救救我
Help me!
救命
Help!
朱尼尔 你的舅舅在哪
Junior, where's your uncle?
发生了什么
What happened?
我不知道 山姆在哪
I don't know! Where's Sam?
山姆
Sam!
把她放到桌子上
Put her down on the table.
到厨房拿我的急救箱过来
Get my EMT bag from the kitchen.
地震时她突然倒下了
She collapsed during the earthquake.
她的脉搏很虚弱
Her pulse is weak.
呼吸很浅
Shallow breathing...
我们得恢复她的心跳
We gotta get her heart rate up.
你的脸怎么了
What happened to your face?
不用担心这个
Don't worry about it.
快拿阿托品过来 它在瓶子里
Atropine! It's in the vial.
阿托品来了
It's atropine.
梅勒妮
Melanie...
它要多久才起作用
How long before it works?
你拿了那个蛋吗
Did you take the egg?
没有
No.
它不见了吗
Is it gone?
可能乔和诺瑞拿了
Maybe Joe and Norrie have it.
噢 我希望他们没事
Oh, I just hope they're okay.
-我们应该去找他们 -对
- We should go find them. - BARBIE: Yeah.
嘿 陪着她
Hey, stay with her.
还有 山姆 别再让她出事
And, Sam, don't let anything happen to her.
她的脉搏还是比正常的要虚弱
Her pulse is still weaker than it should be.
现在 她需要的就是休息
Right now, what she needs is rest.
穹顶没事
The dome was right.
如果我早点杀了你 她就会死
If I'd killed you earlier, she'd be dead.
是啊 如果我不能
Yeah, well, she still might
让她保持稳定她还是可能会死
be if I don't find a way to keep her stable.
她是其中一只手 你最好做好点
She's one of the hands. You better.
这安全吗
Is it safe?
起码比呆在这安全
Safer than staying down here.
大吉姆在这等挺好的
Nice of Big Jim to wait.
来吧 来吧 我抓到你了
Come on. Come on, I got you.
-拉我起来 -来吧
- Pull me up! - Come on!
我抓着你
I got you!
来吧
Come on.
你没事吧
You okay?
这地震是什么回事
What the hell was that earthquake?
你不会想知道的
You don't want to know.
趁地震再来之前我们还是赶快出去吧
Let's get out of here in case another one happens.
没错 走吧
Yeah. Come on.
我以为你去拍照了
I thought you went to take photos.
我忘记拿我的电池了
I forgot my battery pack.
幸好 对吧
Good thing, huh?
是的
- Yeah. -
波林
Pauline.
波琳 你没事吧
Pauline, are you okay?
它们不见了
They're gone.
什么不见了
What's gone?
我的影像
My visions.
地震来的那一刻它们就停止了
The minute the earthquake hit, they stopped.
好吧 我们走吧 来吧 我们先出去
Well, let's go. Come on, let's get out of here.
现在我不知道接下来会发生什么
I don't know what's gonna happen now.
我知道
I do.
我们会去接朱尼尔 我们会是跳下悬崖的头三个人
We go get Junior and we're the first three over the cliffs.
好吗
Okay?
我告诉另一边的军队 我会给他他想要的
I tell the guard on the other side I gave him what he wanted.
那个蛋不再尖叫了
The egg stopped screaming.
我知道
I know.
因为我把它扔下去了 扔到了顶点镇
Because I threw it over the cliff. To Zenith.
-不 -我为了
- No... - I did it...
我为了你做的 我为了
I did it for you. I did it...
不 吉姆
No, Jim.
不
No.
你做了什么
What have you done?
乔和诺瑞肯定在别的什么地方
Joe and Norrie have to be here somewhere.
芭比 茱莉亚
Barbie, Julia!
大吉姆逼我们把蛋扔下了悬崖
Big Jim made us throw the egg off the cliff.
-他做了什么 -他有枪
- He did what? - He had a gun.
好吧 我们走吧 来吧
All right, let's go. Come on.
菲尔
Phil!
菲尔 停下
Phil, stop!
芭比 拿着
Barbie, here!
小心
Careful.
他不见了
He's gone.
什么
What the...?
现在见得到底了
There's a bottom now.
那个蛋没了
The egg's gone.
通道也关闭了
The passage closed.
我们困在这了
We're stuck here.